{
	"HTML": [
		{
			"Question": "What is the purpose of the `<div>` element in HTML?",
			"Answers": [
				"To divide the HTML document into sections",
				"To style elements",
				"To create links",
				"To insert images"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does the `<!DOCTYPE html>` declaration do?",
			"Answers": [
				"It defines the document type and version of HTML",
				"It links CSS file",
				"It creates a new element",
				"None of the above"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
			"Answers": ["`br`", "`break`", "`lb`", "`br`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the purpose of the `<meta>` tag in HTML?",
			"Answers": [
				"To provide metadata about the HTML document",
				"To style elements",
				"To create links",
				"To insert images"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the purpose of the `href` attribute in an `<a>` element in HTML?",
			"Answers": [
				"To specify the URL or destination that the link should navigate to when clicked",
				"To style elements",
				"To create links",
				"To insert images"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a list item?",
			"Answers": ["`li`", "`listitem`", "`list-item`", "`br`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a table header?",
			"Answers": ["`th`", "`header`", "`tableheader`", "`table-header`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a table data cell?",
			"Answers": ["`td`", "`data`", "`tabledata`", "`table-data`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a form input field?",
			"Answers": ["`input`", "`field`", "`inputfield`", "`input-field`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a form submit button?",
			"Answers": [
				"`input type='submit'`",
				"`button type='submit'`",
				"`input-button type='submit'`",
				"`button-input type='submit'`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for an image?",
			"Answers": ["`img`", "`picture`", "`image`", "`img-tag`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a video?",
			"Answers": ["`video`", "`videotag`", "`videoelement`", "`video-tag`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a script?",
			"Answers": ["`script`", "`scripttag`", "`scriptelement`", "`script-tag`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a style?",
			"Answers": ["`style`", "`styletag`", "`styleelement`", "`style-tag`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a header?",
			"Answers": ["`header`", "`Header`", "`headers`", "`HEADER`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a footer?",
			"Answers": ["`footer`", "`footers`", "`Footer`", "`FOOTER`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a navigation bar?",
			"Answers": ["`nav`", "`navbar`", "`navigation`", "`nav-bar`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a section?",
			"Answers": ["`section`", "`Section`", "`SECTION`", "`sections`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a main content area?",
			"Answers": ["`main`", "`mains`", "`Main`", "`MAIN`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a sidebar?",
			"Answers": ["`asides`", "`sidebar`", "`Aside`", "`aside`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 3
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct HTML element for a details summary?",
			"Answers": ["`Details`", "`summary`", "`details`", "`summary`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 2
		}
	],

	"CSS": [
		{
			"Question": "What does CSS stand for?",
			"Answers": [
				"Cascading Style Sheets",
				"Computer Style Sheets",
				"Colorful Style Sheets",
				"Creative Style Sheets"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "Where in an HTML document is the correct place to refer to an external style sheet?",
			"Answers": [
				"In the `<body>` section",
				"At the end of the document",
				"In the `<head>` section",
				"In the `<footer>` section"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS syntax?",
			"Answers": [
				"`body:color=black;`",
				"`body {color: black;}`",
				"`{body;color:black;}`",
				"`{body:color=black;}`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct way to add a comment in a CSS file?",
			"Answers": [
				"`/*This is a comment*/`",
				"`//This is a comment`",
				"`!--This is a comment--`",
				"`!This is a comment`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does the `!important` rule in CSS do?",
			"Answers": [
				"It makes a CSS rule more important than other rules",
				"It makes a CSS rule less important than other rules",
				"It makes a CSS rule apply to all elements",
				"It makes a CSS rule apply to no elements"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the text color?",
			"Answers": ["`color`", "`text-color`", "`font-color`", "`text-colour`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the background color?",
			"Answers": [
				"`background-color`",
				"`bg-color`",
				"`background-colour`",
				"`bg-colour`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the font size?",
			"Answers": ["`font-size`", "`text-size`", "`font-scale`", "`text-scale`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the font family?",
			"Answers": ["`font-family`", "`text-font`", "`font-face`", "`text-face`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the font weight?",
			"Answers": [
				"`font-weight`",
				"`text-weight`",
				"`font-strength`",
				"`text-strength`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the text alignment?",
			"Answers": [
				"`text-align`",
				"`align-text`",
				"`text-position`",
				"`align-position`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the margin?",
			"Answers": ["`margin`", "`space`", "`padding`", "`border`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the padding?",
			"Answers": ["`padding`", "`space`", "`margin`", "`border`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the border?",
			"Answers": [
				"`border`",
				"`border-style`",
				"`border-color`",
				"`border-width`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the width?",
			"Answers": ["`width`", "`size`", "`length`", "`dimension`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the height?",
			"Answers": ["`height`", "`size`", "`length`", "`dimension`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the box-sizing?",
			"Answers": [
				"`box-sizing`",
				"`box-size`",
				"`box-dimension`",
				"`box-length`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the position?",
			"Answers": ["`position`", "`location`", "`place`", "`spot`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct CSS property to change the display?",
			"Answers": ["`display`", "`show`", "`view`", "`showcase`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		}
	],

	"JS": [
		{
			"Question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
			"Answers": ["`javascript`", "`js`", "`scripting`", "`script`"],
			"CorrectAnswer": 3
		},
		{
			"Question": "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called `xxx.js`?",
			"Answers": [
				"`script href='xxx.js'`",
				"`script name='xxx.js'`",
				"`script src='xxx.js'`",
				"`script file='xxx.js'`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"Question": "How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"`function:myFunction()`",
				"`function = myFunction()`",
				"`function myFunction()`",
				"`myFunction:function()`"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `===` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Checks if two values are equal",
				"Checks if two values are not equal",
				"Checks if two values are the same type",
				"Checks if two values are not the same type"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `==` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Checks if two values are equal",
				"Checks if two values are not equal",
				"Checks if two values are the same type",
				"Checks if two values are not the same type"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `!=` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Checks if two values are not equal",
				"Checks if two values are equal",
				"Checks if two values are the same type",
				"Checks if two values are not the same type"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `!==` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Checks if two values are not equal",
				"Checks if two values are equal",
				"Checks if two values are not the same type",
				"Checks if two values are the same type"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `&&` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a logical AND operation",
				"Performs a logical OR operation",
				"Performs a logical NOT operation",
				"Performs a logical XOR operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `||` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a logical OR operation",
				"Performs a logical AND operation",
				"Performs a logical NOT operation",
				"Performs a logical XOR operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `!` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a logical NOT operation",
				"Performs a logical AND operation",
				"Performs a logical OR operation",
				"Performs a logical XOR operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `>>` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a right shift operation",
				"Performs a left shift operation",
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation",
				"Performs a bitwise OR operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `<<` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a left shift operation",
				"Performs a right shift operation",
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation",
				"Performs a bitwise OR operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `>>>` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a zero-fill right shift operation",
				"Performs a left shift operation",
				"Performs a right shift operation",
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `&` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation",
				"Performs a logical AND operation",
				"Performs a bitwise OR operation",
				"Performs a logical OR operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `|` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a bitwise OR operation",
				"Performs a logical OR operation",
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation",
				"Performs a logical AND operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `^` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a bitwise XOR operation",
				"Performs a logical XOR operation",
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation",
				"Performs a logical AND operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `~` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a bitwise NOT operation",
				"Performs a logical NOT operation",
				"Performs a bitwise AND operation",
				"Performs a logical AND operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `+` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs an addition operation",
				"Performs a subtraction operation",
				"Performs a multiplication operation",
				"Performs a division operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `-` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a subtraction operation",
				"Performs an addition operation",
				"Performs a multiplication operation",
				"Performs a division operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `*` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a multiplication operation",
				"Performs an addition operation",
				"Performs a subtraction operation",
				"Performs a division operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		},
		{
			"Question": "What does `/` operator do in JavaScript?",
			"Answers": [
				"Performs a division operation",
				"Performs an addition operation",
				"Performs a subtraction operation",
				"Performs a multiplication operation"
			],
			"CorrectAnswer": 0
		}
	]
}
